<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="ble_remote_control_c1_button_custom_title_txt">C1 button customisation</string>
    <string name="ble_remote_control_dialog_error_bluetooth_off_txt">Pairing cancelled because Bluetooth was turned off</string>
    <string name="ble_remote_control_endurance_mode_dialog_main_message_txt">The device temperature may increase above typical operating temperature. When the temperature increases, a notification and icon will alert you. In this case, don’t hold the device in your hand. Please make sure the remote control is connected via Bluetooth before continuing.</string>
    <string name="ble_remote_control_pair_new_controller_description_txt">"To start pairing, interact with the remote controller.
You will receive notifications and dialogues two times. Select PAIR on all of them, then press any key on the paired device to finish pairing."</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_color_and_brightness_txt">Colour and brightness</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_common_error_internal_memory_full_txt">Internal storage full. Save data on SD card instead?</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_common_error_internal_memory_unavailable_txt">Internal storage is corrupt or write-protected. Save data on SD card instead?</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_cooling_mode_message2_txt">Please wait for your device to cool down, then restart the camera.</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_custom_ael_txt">AEL button customisation</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_custom_disp_txt">DISP button customisation</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_custom_fn_txt">Function menu customisation</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_dialog_battery_level_low_recording_txt">Recording has stopped due to low battery. Charge your device and try again.</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_dialog_body_qrcode_wifi_ready_airplane_on_txt">"Aeroplane mode is on.
Please turn off Aeroplane mode from SETTINGS."</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_dialog_body_qrcode_wifi_ready_details_name_txt">"Network name: 
"</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_dialog_body_qrcode_wifi_ready_wifi_off_airplane_on_txt">"Wi-Fi is turned off and Aeroplane mode is turned on.
Please change these settings by tapping on SETTINGS."</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_dialog_title_qrcode_wifi_connecting_txt">Connecting...</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_dialog_title_qrcode_wifi_ready_details_password_txt">"
Password protection: 
"</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_dialog_title_qrcode_wifi_ready_details_security_txt">"
Security: 
"</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_dialog_user_data_collection_txt">If you agree below, Sony will collect your &lt;b>&lt;a href=#personal-data>personal data&lt;/a>&lt;/b> to provide customised support and improve devices and services. Sony will handle your data per our &lt;b>&lt;a href=https://www.sonymobile.com/privacy/>Privacy Policy&lt;/a>&lt;/b>.</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_dialog_video_hdr_hlg_supported_txt">You can record videos even in high contrast scene, and make them more dramatic and closer to what you see in real life. Please use supported devices/services to enjoy the content with its original colour and brightness.</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_dro_hdr_description_txt">This setting will optimise the range of values. DRO processing uses a single image, whereas Auto HDR combines multiple exposures to achieve the result.</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_dro_hdr_dro_txt">D-Range Optimiser</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_error_internal_sd_full_txt">Memory full. Delete some files from SD card or internal storage.</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_face_eye_af_settings_on_txt">Face detection/Eye AF on</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_feature_drive_mode_description_txt">The drive mode can be changed to use Single or Continuous shooting, or the self-timer.</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_feature_hand_shutter_description_txt">"Turn your palm towards the camera. The self-timer will start counting down when your palm is recognised. To make it easier to detect, extend your fingers upward.
To enable this function, switch to the front camera while in Basic (photo) mode and turn on Hand shutter in MENU."</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_feature_lens_correction_description_txt">"When using the ultra-wide lens (0.7x), you can select a priority. By selecting Prioritise image quality, you can capture dynamic high-quality images. If you select Prioritise correction for distortion, you can reduce visual distortion.
This function is active when taking photos using the ultra-wide lens. After switching to the ultra-wide lens, you can configure the priority from MENU > Ultra-wide lens correction."</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_feature_triple_camera_switch_with_3_lenses_description_txt">"You can easily switch between camera lenses to capture any situation to challenge your creativity.
Tap the button in the viewfinder to switch between 0.7x (ultra-wide), 1.0x (wide), and 2.1x (standard) lenses.
You can use this function in both Basic (Photo) and Basic (Video) mode."</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_flash_torch_off_txt">Torch: Off</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_flash_torch_on_txt">Torch: On</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_flash_torch_txt">Torch</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_focus_area_center_txt">Centre</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_focus_frame_color_description_txt">Set the colour of the focus area frame</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_focus_frame_color_txt">Focus area colour</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_focus_mode_mf_txt">Manual focus</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_hand_shutter_txt">Hand shutter</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_lens_correction_description_txt">When using the ultra-wide lens, you can select a priority. By selecting Prioritise image quality, you can capture dynamic high-quality images. If you select Prioritise correction for distortion, you can reduce visual distortion.</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_lens_correction_off_txt">Prioritise image quality</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_lens_correction_on_txt">Prioritise correction for distortion</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_max_file_size_save_failed_txt">Recording stopped due to maximum file size limitation</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_max_recording_time_save_failed_txt">Recording stopped because of a maximum recording time limitation</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_menu_sub_photo_front_txt">Photo (front)</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_menu_sub_video_front_txt">Video (front)</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_menu_tab_exposure_color_txt">Exposure/Colour</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_metering_center_txt">Centre</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_mode_basic_description_txt">"In this mode you can take photos using the onscreen shutter button, similar to the usual smartphone camera experience.
Use this mode to take selfies, shoot videos, and scan QR codes."</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_mode_mr_p_fullname_txt">Programme auto (Memory recall)</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_mode_p_fullname_txt">Programme auto</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_multi_window_txt">Drag the middle of the split bar to switch to full-screen %1$s to use</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_qrcode_detect_text_notsupported_txt">This QR Code is not supported</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_restricted_setting_continuous_hi_unavailable_for_current_lens_txt">Cannot use Continuous shooting: High with the currently selected lens</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_restricted_setting_continuous_unavailable_for_bokeh_effect_txt">Cannot select Continuous shooting while using Bokeh effect</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_restricted_setting_flashlight_unavailable_for_current_lens_txt">Cannot use Torch with the currently selected lens</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_runtime_permission_rationale_location_txt">To retrieve locations</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_runtime_permission_rationale_microphone_txt">To record sounds</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_soft_skin_effect_txt">Soft Skin Effect</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_sw_license_txt">Software licence</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_tutorial_page1_description_txt">"Sony is a brand beloved by photographers for creating products that spread the endless joy and wonder of photography.
Our experience and technology continues to be chosen by customers around the world.

Photography Pro seeks to recreate the operability and functions of full-scale cameras from Sony Imaging Products.
Sony supports your photographic creativity."</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_tutorial_page2_description_txt">"Choose the ideal Shooting mode to match your subject.
Next, set the shutter speed and exposure.
Hold the camera steady from the sides, and take a picture.

Shooting modes include:
P (Programme auto)
S (Shutter speed priority)
M (Manual exposure)"</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_tutorial_page3_description_txt">"When using Auto/P/S/M modes, firmly hold the camera in landscape orientation and press the shutter button on the upper right hand side of the device to take photos.

Selecting Auto will set functions like shutter speed and exposure automatically.

To configure settings manually, select one of the modes below.
P (Programme auto)
S (Shutter speed priority)
M (Manual exposure)"</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_video_explanatory_4k2k_setting_txt">For stable 4K video recording, you must not change this setting unless you use a high-speed SD card (UHS Speed Class 1 or higher, or Speed Class 10 are recommended).</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_video_explanatory_slowmotion_setting_txt">"For stable slow-motion video recording, don't change this setting unless you use a high-speed SD card (UHS Speed Class 1 or higher, or Speed Class 10 are recommended)."</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_video_explanatory_txt">"For stable video recording, we recommend that you change data storage to Internal storage. Would you like to change now?

If you continue to use SD card as data storage, make sure that you use a high-speed SD card (UHS Speed Class 1 or higher, or Speed Class 10 recommended)."</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_video_file_format_4k_txt">File format (4K)</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_video_stabilization_description_txt">The Xperia has a unique hybrid stabilisation system called Optical SteadyShot - combining optical image stabilisation and electronic image stabilisation simultaneously. It gives you shake free and smooth videos even when recording on the move.</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_video_stabilization_txt">Video stabilisation</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_whitebalance_button_set_txt">Apply</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_whitebalance_cwb_description_txt">Set white balance based on the centre of the preview</string>
    <string name="photopro_strings_whitebalance_cwb_title_txt">Apply - %1$s</string>
</resources>
